They take it so seriously,
他们对赛车极其认真，
whereas in Europe and America,
而在欧洲和美国，
you get the sense that it's all part of a lifestyle.
赛车对很多人而言更像是一种生活方式。
They want to experience the life of a racing driver.
他们想体验职业车手的生活，
They want to wear the right watch.
想戴一块体面的腕表，
They want to hang out with the right drivers.
想与圈内的车手交往，
They want to dine well,
想品尝美食，
and they want to have a cool life.
过一种很酷的生活。
The drivers here take it so much more seriously.
但这里的车手对比赛要认真得多。
In every single session,
每一个赛段，
the AM drivers are looking at the lap times,
AM级车手都会研究圈速，
looking at the data,
分析赛车数据，
trying to figure out
努力找出，
where they can make their throttle inputs a little more precise.
哪些位置的油门输入还可以更加精准。
They're watching championships from around the world,
他们会关注世界各地的锦标赛，
as well as other GT championships,
也会研究其他GT赛事，
to figure out how to become better at their craft.
从中钻研如何进一步提升驾驶技术。
And no one in that category is more dedicated than Wang Yibo.
在这类车手中，王一博尤其投入。
Just 12 months ago, he was still a driver getting used to the sport.
就在一年前，他还是一名尚在适应这项运动的车手。
Now he eats, breathes and sleeps motorsport.
如今，他的生活完全围绕着赛车运动。
He is absolutely hooked,
他已经彻底痴迷其中，
and he wants to win this championship.
而且渴望赢得这项锦标赛。
Whether it's this year or next year,
无论是在今年还是明年，
he is absolutely determined and resolute.
他的目标都无比明确，决心也异常坚定。
He wants to become a China GT champion.
他希望成为China GT冠军。
So, as the fans make their voices heard in the stands,
此刻，看台上的车迷仍在高声呐喊，
we get ready for the next encounter,
我们也准备迎接下一场较量，
which is the second qualifying session.
也就是第二节排位赛。
And the battle really is raging.
赛场上的争夺正愈演愈烈。